A waiter has returned a cheque worth nearly $424,000 to a retired social worker who
lost it. A waiter has returned a cheque worth nearly $424,000 to a retired social
worker who lost it.
The waiter found a bank envelope while cleaning off a table last Saturday at a
He ran outside but the customer was gone.
The waiter found a bank envelope while cleaning off a last Saturday at a restaurant.
He opened the envelope and got a shock.
After an unsuccessful search, the restaurant's owner called the Daily News for help.
The relieved customer was reunited with her cheque on Wednesday.
It contained money from her apartment sale, already planned for a down payment on a
new home. The relieved customer was reunited with her cheque on Wednesday.
contained money from her apartment sale, already planned for a down payment on a new
home. The relieved customer was reunited with her cheque on Wednesday.
It contained money from her apartment sale, already planned for a down payment on a
new home. The customer did not tip the waiter after her meal.
She tried to give him money later on but he graciously declined.
The customer did not tip the waiter after her meal.
The customer did not tip the after her meal.
She tried to give him money later on but he graciously declined.
waiter, who's working his way through school, did accept the customer's apology and
gratitude and said he was happy to have helped her.
The waiter, who's working his way through school, did accept the customer's apology
and gratitude and said he was happy to have helped her.